(Penny:)So should we talk
to each other or mingle?
(Amy:)I don't know where everyone is.
(Penny:)Yeah, I mean,
(Penny:)I could see him eating
one or two guests,
(Penny:)but not a whole party.
(Bert:)Well, I guess this is
kind of a bust.
(Bert:)You don't have to stay.
(Bert:)I'm gonna start cleaning up.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Amy:)I feel so bad about
leaving him here.
(Penny:)Oh, it's funny, I was just thinking
the same thing about you.
(Bert:)Hey, listen,
(Bert:)could you not
say anything about this
(Bert:)to the people at the university?
(Bert:)You know, 'cause...
(Bert:)you're you and I'm me,
and it's kind of embarrassing.
(Penny:)Wait, what do you mean
"she's her"?
(Bert:)Well, you know how Amy's the
coolest girl on campus, right?
(Howard:)No.
No.
(Bert:)Oh yeah, everybody thinks so.
(Howard:)What?
(Penny:)You tell me about your foot
fungus, but this is a secret?